timtales.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Timtales by Tim Kruger

This privacy policy declares in an easy and not too technical way what kind of data is collected and tracked at Timtales.com when you interact with the site.

**Data collection and purpose**

When you purchase a membership our billing providers Epoch.com and Segpay.com will gather the payment information you provide so the purchase can be processed. They are using the latest technology to protect your data. Please refer to the privacy statements of www.Epoch.com or www.Segpay.com for more information.

After a signup for a membership the billing providers Epoch or Segpay will disclose some of the information they gathered from you to us at Timtales. This information contains your email address, your name, your join country and postal code, the membership type you purchased and the payment method you used.

It does NOT contain any exact address and it does NOT contain your credit card number, bank account number or any other specific bank details.

We use the information provided by the billing companies only if there is a problem with your membership or your login or if you contact us for support. We guarantee that we will NOT rent, sell, or share personal information about you with any third party, except when required by law, like by a subpoena or court order.

There is also information we collect and save on our own server when you interact with the site. When your reach the site as a visitor, we record which site you have visited before. This helps us to determine if a banner that we placed on a partner site brought you to us or maybe some posts we made on social media.

When you login to your membership account we record your IP address and date and time of your access. Also we see which pages and videos you view and the amount of data you download.

We also see the browser and operating system that you use to view our content.

We do this to diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the website. Also it helps gather general demographic information that helps us improve our product. Example: By recording which operating system our members use we had learned that we had to improve our site for use on mobile devices like iPhone and Android phones.

Furthermore, we place cookies in our members area. They are necessary to manage your online session. Example: The cookie tells the system that your are still logged in whenever you watch another video. Otherwise you would get the login dialogue over and over again when you watch or download multiple videos. Also, cookies tell us which videos you have saved as favourites in your account, so you find them again in your “my favourites” page whenever you login. You can set your browser not to accept cookies. However, then the site will not function properly. You can also delete cookies in your browser after a session on a website. That will be no problem for your next online session.

And finally, we use Google Analytics to get information about our site statistics. The information that Google uses for that cannot be used to identify you personally. It is general information that shows things like: What is the time when we have the most site visitors, Where do the visitors come from, How many visitor do we have on a specific day.

This kind of statistic information guides us to make the necessary adjustments to our site and our content to make the user experience more pleasurable and bring our hot videos to more people all around the world.

**Under age**

Our services are directed to adults who possess validated credit card information, and are not marketed to individuals under the age of eighteen (or twenty-one in territories where twenty-one is the legal age ). Timtales has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information from individuals under age.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

You can rest assured that we lock each and every information we have on our servers behind a wall of the latest security technology. We make every security update of our software in the moment it is released.

**Access to your personal information**

You have the right to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold about you. To request access please contact us here. We will provide the information free of charge and within one month, except in the event that the request is unfounded, excessive or repetitive, in which case we reserve the right to charge a proportionate administration fee or refuse.

**Rectification of personal information**

If any of the information we hold on you is inaccurate or incomplete, you may ask us to correct or complete it at any time.

**Your right of erasure, or to be forgotten**

You may request the deletion of any email we hold on you at any time. To request deletion of your personal information, contact us using the email address we hold for you or otherwise proving your identity.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, you’ll need to check that site’s privacy statement.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Timtales.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.

**Contact us**

Further customer service questions? Please use our contact form to send us a request. We will be happy to assist you.
